《死神来了5》
早安 各位员工
Good morning, Presage employees.
希望你们准备好参加令人兴奋的团队建设培训
We hope you're all ready for our exciting team-building retraining.
请享用您的早餐
Please enjoy your breakfast..
然后我们上车 很快就会出发
and then make your way to the bus, which will leave shortly.
山姆 我说 "你能为培训准备一些早餐吗?"
Hey, Sam, I said, "Would you put breakfast together for the retraining?"...
我的意思是弄些甜麦圈 还有咖啡 之类的
I meant, like, some stale doughnuts, some coffee.
你做的太棒了
But this is amazing.
谢谢 兄弟 别忘了我上个月的销售报告
Thanks, man. Just remember that when you see my sales report for last month.
- 我昨晚看见到了 - 该死!
- Oh, I saw it last night. - Shit.
丹尼斯看了?
Has Dennis seen it?
还没有
Not yet.
你还是需要做个决定 知道吗?
Look, you just need to make a decision, you know?
你可以做厨师 或是做业务员
You gonna be "chef" or you gonna be "sales guy".
作为朋友 我才这么说 如是你的老板 我早开除你了
I'm saying that as your friend because, as your boss, I'm ready to fire your ass.
- 作为朋友 我很感激这个建议 - 好的
- As your friend, I appreciate that advice. - Good.
我宝宝的房里
Inside my baby's room
等一下 我马上就回来
Hold on, man, I'll be right back.
我想我做的不错
Yeah, I guess I'm doing okay
我走进…
I moved in with..
茉莉 你的车票被取消了
Molly. Your ticket's canceled.
告诉我这只是一个误会
Tell me that's a mistake.
我原想过完这个周末告诉你
I was gonna tell you after this weekend.
呃 告诉我什么?
Uh, tell me what?
我觉得这不是 一个好主意
That I don't think it's such a good idea.
什么 旅行吗? 这是我兄弟的婚礼
What, the trip? it's my brother's wedding.
出什么事了?
What's going on here?
我们应该晚点再谈论这件事 我们…
We should talk about this later. Let's just..
什么 接下来的两天我都假装没看到这个? 就现在说吧
What, pretend like I didn't see this for the next two days? No, let's talk about this.
不会有结果的 山姆
It's not working out, Sam.
我们不会有结果的
We're not working out.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
呃 你是坎蒂丝 对吗?
Oh, it's, uh, Candice, right?
- 一点都不好笑 - 哦
- Not funny. - Oh..
抱歉 这次不是度假 是一次商务培训
Okay, sorry, this is not a vacation. Okay, this is a business retraining.
我们接下来的两天 面对的都将是公事
So we're gonna be all business for the next two days.
对不起
Sorry.
我爱你 不过这不能改变你还是一个实习生
I love you, but doesn't change the fact that you're still an intern.
唔 今晚十二点三十分宵禁 你要准备好出来
Oh, um, but that 12:30 curfew tonight. You should plan on breaking that.
为何?
Why?
我们"袒胸"团队合作
For the naked team-building.
奥莉维亚
Hey, Olivia.
别忘了这个
Don't forget this.
好的 我会记住的
Oh, yeah. I keep trying to.
- 嗯 - 我喜欢它 有点莉萨乐步的感觉
- Hmm. - I like it. it's very Lisa Loeb.
哦 你知道
Oh, well, you know..
我更喜欢做自己
I'd rather be very Olivia.
我们周日要办一个音乐会
We got a gig on Sunday.
好 我一定会来
Yeah, I'll be there.
早 彼特
Morning, Peter.
- 看起来精神不错 - 嗨
- Looking good. - Uh, hi.
奥莉维亚 你和城里每个时髦的人都睡了吗?
Olivia. Have you slept with every hipster in town yet?
坎蒂丝 你应该为这次实习买单
Candice. Do you actually get paid for this internship..
还是你老爸多给你零用钱了?
or does Daddy just increase your allowance?
如果你想摆脱婴儿肥 你应该去健身房
You know, if you wanna get rid of that baby fat, you should try the gym.
他们的设备有些落后 不过你依然可以使用
They have these workout machines that you use on your back.
对你有帮助
You're good at that.
亲爱的 这不是胖
Sweetie, it's not fat.
他们称之为爆乳
They're called tits.
你看起来不太好? 茉莉
You're not looking so hot there, Moll-face.
是的 谢谢
Gee, thanks.
你尝了你男朋友做的果酱面包吗?
Did you try the little jam-bread whatever your boyfriend made?
我得告诉你 他真的… 怎么了? 我碰到了神经?
I gotta tell you, he's a pre.. Uh-oh, that's what it is, is it? Did I touch a nerve?
- 让我安静下 艾萨克 - 摩尔 摩尔 看着我
- Just leave me alone, Isaac. - Hey, Moll? Moll? Look at me.
如果你想找人聊聊…
If you ever need anyone to talk to..
我是很好的倾听者… 嘘 等下 别说话
I've been told I'm a good listener by a lot of ladies. Shh, wait. Don't say anything.
你是上星期二的津博吗?
Tell me this is Kimber from last Tuesday.
对不起 是哪个津博? 等一下公交车上我们坐在一起
Wait, I'm sorry, which Kimber is... Hey, let's sit next to each other on the bus.
不 我记得你 你是一个大女孩 对吗?
No, no, I remember you. You were, like, a bigger gal, right?
你知道该做什么吗? 你应该道歉
You know what you should do? You should apologize.
- 为什么 - 没关系的
- Why? - Doesn't matter.
别介意 就说"对不起 因为我…"
Never matters. "I'm sorry, because I.."
妈的!
Oh, shit.
斯坦 你怎么了?
Hey, Stan, how's it going?
呃 我叫山姆 先生
Uh, it's Sam, sir.
你在纠正我吗
Did you just correct me?
不是
No.
看着我
Look at me.
- 我叫什么名字 - 丹尼斯
- What's my name? - Dennis.
别看了
Look away.
都准备好了吗 彼特?
All set, Pete?
当然 先生 我在等内森
Yes, sir. Yeah, we're just waiting on Nathan.
什么事是无法循环的 彼特?
What's the one thing we can't recycle, Pete?
浪费时间 先生
Wasted time, sir.
当然 我想在90秒之内出发
Exactly. I wanna be on the road in 90 seconds.
我刚刚看见他的车了 我去找他
Uh, well, I just saw his car, so I'll go track him down.
你很有进取心 斯坦
Way to show some initiative, Stan.
今天会是个好日子的
It's gonna be a good day.
- 嗨 伙计们 - 嗨 伙计
- Hey, guys. - Hey, man.
怎么样 兄弟
What's up, bud?
为什么这么缠着内特 伙计
Why you riding Nate so hard, man?
我只是想搞清状况
You know, I'm just trying to make sense of it here.
三周前 他们给你买了一本《客户经理助理艺术》
Three weeks ago they brought you in as assistant plant manager..
- 现在又让你休假? - 不是休假
- and now you got a day off? - It's not a day off.
是一个弱…弱…
It's a re.. Re..
弱…什么? 弱智?
Re.. Re-what? Retarded?
- 是培训 - 是培训
- It's a retraining. - It's a retraining.
我并不想去 只是服从命令而已
I don't wanna go. I'm just following orders.
- 如果你不喜欢 你可以… - 我能什么 我能做什么?
- So if you don't like it, then you can.. - I can what? What? I can what?
内森 快来吧!我们都在等你
Nathan, hey. Come on, man, we're all waiting for you.
- 好!好吧 - 等一等 你有什么想说的?
- Yeah, okay. - No, hold on. What you gonna say?
你有什么想说的
What you gonna say?
我比你多做至少15年
I got 15 years on you here.
你做什么了? 四年就坐到办公室的位置?
You got, what, four years in some classroom upstate?
听着 你认为我想坐到…
Listen, if you think I'm gonna sit here..
罗伊 这不是好办法 伙计
Not a good idea, Roy. Not a good idea, man.
我们今天可以的
We're fine for the day.
为什么让他这么做?
Why do you let him get away with that?
我别无选择 他是工会代表
No choice. He's the union rep.
我开除他 就会得罪罗伊他们一伙人
I fire him and suddenly I've got a factory full of Roys.
即使他要杀了我 我也会搞定他
But I'll win him over, even if it kills me.
你怎么样了?
What about you?
什么时候让你在餐馆正式工作?
When are they gonna offer you that permanent gig at the restaurant?
- 已经好了 - 兄弟 那太好了!
- They already did. - Dude, that's great.
我不知道
I don't know, man.
我是说 他们想把我派到巴黎的旗舰店
I mean, they wanna send me to the flagship restaurant in Paris..
谁知道会做多久? 可能一年半载的
for who knows how long? Could be six months, could be a year.
我觉得我将舍弃很多
I just thought I'd be leaving too much behind.
现在我还没确定
Although now I'm not so sure.
如果去巴黎 帮我一个忙
Well, look, if you do go to Paris, do me a favor.
- 什么? - 带罗伊一起去
- What's that? - Take Roy with you.
哦 没必要
Aw, hell, no.
嘿 山姆
Hey, Sam.
上来吗?
You coming?
是的
Yeah.
准备好参加180企业咨询的拓展
Get ready for a new adventure at 180 Corporate Consulting.
接下来两天将进行身体和心理上的测试
For the next two days, you will be tested, both physically and mentally..
帮你触发真正的潜能
to help you reach your true potential..
通过与团队一起活动
through working as part of your corporate team.
这个周末 专家将指导你 达到更好的效果
This weekend, a professional will guide you to achieving better results ..
这有什么用处?
What are those for?
哦 可以帮助我放松
Oh, it's, um, just something I do to relax me.
还有好运
And for luck.
体操运动员比棒球选手更相信这个
Gymnasts are worse than baseball players at this kind of thing.
她很迷信
She's superstitious.
嗨!卡特丽娜 你好吗?
Hey, Katrina, how you doing?
不好 这种培训真是个馊主意 那些办公室的白痴
Nah, just this stupid retraining thing with the idiots from the office.
不 不 不是你 先生!是他们
No, no, no, not you, sir. Them.
等我一下 我去一个安静的地方再说
Hold on a sec, let me go someplace a little more private.
光头是新的潮流 先生 光头是新的潮流
Bald's the new black, sir. Bald's the new black.
呃 等一下 等我进了办公室
Yeah, no, hang on a sec, babe. Just gonna head on back to my private office.
走右边
The right-hand side!
喔
Whew.
哦 该死!
Ow. Damn it.
对于管理人员 需要有价值的技巧…
For management, the valuable skills necessary..
培养成一个成功的领导者可以通过多种…
for being a good leader will be cultivated through a variety..
∮ 风中灰尘 ∮
∮ Dust in the wind ∮
∮ 我们都是… ∮
∮ All we are... ∮
我们从远端把它拴上
We'll tie it off from the far side.
哦 哇
Oh, whoa!
噢 妈的!
Whoa, what the hell?
- 彼特 你感觉到了吗? - 什么?
- Peter, did you feel that? - What?
有点不对劲
Something's wrong.
小心
Look out!
茉莉 过来!
Molly, come on.
- 快走 - 快快
- Go! - Go, go!
坎蒂丝!坎蒂丝!
Candice! Candice!
彼特!
Peter!
彼特!彼特!
Peter! Peter!
- 不 坎蒂丝! - 啊
- No, Candice! - Aah!
不!
No!
彼特 快走!彼特 我们走
Peter! Come on, Peter, let's go!
茉莉 快走
Molly, come on!
发生了什么事?
What the fuck?!
不 不不!
Oh, no! No! No!
来吧 我们走
Come on, let's go! Let's go!
妈的!
Oh, Shit!
这边!看到护栏吗?
Over here! See the railing?
你能做得到 来吧
You can do this. Let's go.
来吧!走
Let's go. Do it!
你能做到 别看下面!
You can do it. Don't look down!
很好 很好
Good. Good.
快跑
Run!
救救我!
Help me!
- 山姆 - 奥莉维亚!
- Sam! - Olivia!
奥莉维亚
Olivia!
- 山姆 - 我在这!我在这!
- Sam! - I'm right here. I'm right here. Okay.
要散架了
It's coming loose!
- 感觉到了吗? 好的 - 奥莉维亚 过来!
- Do you feel it? All right. - Olivia, come on.
没事 很安全 你就顺着茉莉的声音过去
it's okay, it's safe. Now you've just gotta follow this to Molly's voice, all right?
过来 继续 就快到了 加油
Come towards me. Come on, you're almost there! Come on.
快点!
Come on.
- 快来 快点 - 茉莉!
- Come on. Come on! - Molly.
不!
No! No!
奥莉维亚!
Olivia!
山姆 等等我们!
Sam! Wait for us!
哦 天呢
Oh, my God!
山姆
Sam!
山姆 小心
Aah! Sam, be careful!
山姆
Sam!
彼特 快点!
Peter! Hurry!
山姆 山姆!
Sam! Sam!
山姆
Sam!
抓住!
Hold on!
快点!快点!
Come on, come on.
山姆 抓住!
Sam, hold on!
彼特!
No! Peter!
该死!
Ow. Damn it.
我们将帮助您构建企业文化 通过限定…
We will help you build a culture of corporate ethics by defining..
风中灰尘
Dust in the wind
…风险管理进程
..risk management process.
我们下车
We all gotta get off.
你知道你在说什么吗?
What are you talking about?
这座桥就要塌了!
The bridge is gonna collapse.
- 什么? - 我们都会死
- What? - We're all gonna die.
到底发生什么事了?
What the hell is going on?
如果现在不离开这座桥 所有人都会死!
We're all gonna die if we don't get off this bridge now!
斯坦 放松 只是一些施工而已
Stan, relax, it's just some construction.
茉莉 求求你 快和我下车
Molly, please. Please, God, follow me.
打开车门!
Open the door.
这是很严重的事 如果他们出事 会算在我们身上 你知道吗
This is a major liability issue. If something happens to them, it's on us, you get that?
- 知道了 - 去找他们
- Yeah. - Then go get that.
好的 好的
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, all right.
山姆 茉莉…
Hey, Sam? Molly?
- 彼特 请和我们一起离开! - 别这样
- Peter, please, just follow. - Come on!
好了 大家都冷静点
Okay, everybody just calm down.
- 我去帮忙 - 拜托 别
- I'm gonna go help. - Please don't.
嗨 伙计们 快点
Hey, guys, come on!
我们走
Let's go!
山姆 回到车上 我们可以再谈谈
Sam, just get back on the bus. We can talk about it.
茉莉 山姆 给我站住!
Molly, Sam, come on, guys.
他上车时就举止怪怪的 你看到了吗?
Did he seem weird to you when he got on the bus?
什么预兆都没有 他突然间就发疯了
No, he was fine. It's like he just snapped.
- 到底怎么了? - 这到底是他妈怎么回事?
- What's going on? - What the hell is going on out here?
我们应该 呃…
We should, uh ..
天啊
Holy shit!
下车
Get off the bus!
快点!
Come on!
你怎么知道的?
How did you know?
这是个很重要的问题
That's the big question here.
你怎么知道的?
How did you know?
在你的口供上清楚的写着
It says right here in your statement:
"我看见桥倒塌,我知道会发生什么事情"
"I saw it collapse. I knew it would happen."
我感觉是有预谋的
That sounds premeditated to me.
不 不 我不是这个意思
No, no, no. That's not what I meant.
我看见了幻象
I had a vision.
好吧 一个幻象
Okay. A vision.
心理现象、鬼魂、大脚怪
Psychic phenomena, ghosts, Bigfoot.
你真的相信这些吗?
You actually believe in that stuff?
我不知道
I don't know.
我告诉你我相信什么
I'll tell you what I believe:
所有事件都有答案
There's an answer for everything.
这需要一个答案 为什么你知道去警告所有人…
There's an answer for why you knew to warn everyone..
桥就要塌了 并且几分钟后 桥真的塌了
the bridge was going to collapse, and minutes later, it did.
我说过 我看见它发生 我不知道怎样看到的
I told you, I saw it coming. I don't know how.
只是看见而已
I just did.
其他人看见了吗?
And no one else did?
我说过 突然就那样发生了
Like I said, it just came out of nowhere.
山姆对当局有意见吗?
Did Sam have issues with authority?
他有没有表现出极端的行为?
Did he ever demonstrate any sort of extremist behavior?
没有
No.
等等 极端行为?
Wait. "Extremist behavior"'?
你的意思是恐怖份子?
You mean like a terrorist?
你看到他那天早上和什么人谈话了吗? 在电话里?
You see him talk to anyone that morning? On a cell phone, pay phone?
他的女友
Just his girlfriend.
他的"前女友" 茉莉
His ex-girlfriend, I mean. Molly.
- 但他们是面对面聊天 - 茉莉
- But that was in person. - Molly.
前女友
Ex.
跟我说说分手的事
Tell me about the breakup.
他很生气? 生气程度从1到10
Was he upset? Scale of 1 to 10.
这是隐私
It's personal.
你一定很生气 是不? 就这样被女友甩了
You must have been pissed, right? Getting dumped like that.
和我所讲的有啥关系呢?
What does that have to do with anything?
我只是搜集所有的难题
I'm just trying to get all the pieces of the puzzle together..
在我开始围绕这些难题采取行动前 解决它们
before I start moving them around, making them fit.
我有一种感觉 会有不好的事情会发生
Look, I just had a hunch that something bad was gonna happen.
就这样
That's it.
不好意思
Excuse me.
法医带回分析报告
Forensics came back with the analysis.
- 怎么说 - 他们认为是大风
- And? - They're chalking it up to high winds..
还有工人把桥面震裂了
and structural damage from the construction.
大风?
"High winds"?
是的 让他们都回家吧
Yeah. Send everyone home.
你可以离开了
You're free to go.
我有种感觉 我们会再见面
I have a feeling we'll be seeing each other again.
这是我的预感
Call it a hunch.
有关部门声明北部湾桥坍塌
Authorities are calling the North Bay Bridge collapse..
是一个奇怪的自然现象
a freak act of nature..
起因是公路改善工程削弱了桥梁结构
citing a highway improvement project that may have weakened the superstructure.
幸存者中有八位Presage造纸厂员工
Among the survivors were eight employees of Presage Paper..
他们原本是去参加商务培训
on their way to a business retraining.
同车的其他17名员工在坍塌中遇难
The other 17 employees were killed in the collapse.
但被称为“幸运8”的幸存员工
And although they've been branded the "lucky eight"...
不得不面对不确定的未来
the surviving employees now face an uncertain future.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
嘿
Hey.
有谁知道什么时候开始?
Anybody know when this thing's supposed to start?
我猜要等丹尼斯到吧
When Dennis gets here, I guess.
那个警察还在纠缠你吗?
That agent still hounding you?
没有 你看了新闻吧 是自然现象造成事故的
No. You heard the news, it was natural causes.
是 我看更像超自然的原因
Yeah, more like supernatural.
你还撑的住吗? 我试着给你打电话
How you holding up? I tried calling.
是的 我看见了 我只是太累了
No, yeah, I saw. I was just tired..
那么…
So?
你会怎么解释?
How did you explain it?
我不解释
I didn't.
我不能解释
I couldn't.
山姆 你必须给个理由
Sam, there had to be a reason.
呵 这就是那个警察一直说的
Heh. That is exactly what the agent kept saying.
无论你们想找什么答案 我没有
Whatever answer you're looking for, I don't have it.
山姆是对的 不管它是如何发生的
Sam's right. It doesn't matter how it happened.
我们把它放到一边 很庆幸我们还活着
We should all just put it behind us and be grateful we're still alive.
这比预见到的结果好 不是吗?
Definitely beats the alternative, right?
今天 看到在这的人
I look out at the faces today..
看到家人和朋友
and I see family members, friends.
但那些在桥上逝去的人 比活着的更多
But the people that left us on the bridge that day, they were more than that.
大家都喜欢珍妮弗 奥尔科特
People like Jennifer Alcott..
克里斯 博伊兰
Chris Boylan..
戴维 巴克勒
David Buckler.
你也许和他们一起工作
Maybe you worked next to them.
也许为他们工作
Maybe you worked for them.
但我们都和他们共事过 恩
But we all worked with them, huh?
谁能忘记特雷弗 维诺的微笑?
Who can forget Trevor Wino's smile?
又或者艾萨克 帕尔默
Or Isaac Palmer.
他在说我的名字?
Did he just say my name?
- 这不好笑 - 我知道 抱歉
- That's not funny. - I know, I'm sorry.
只是感觉这次事故有点怪异 抱歉
I just get weird with tragedies. I'm sorry.
我看见死了的人
I see dead people.
伙计
Guys.
死神
Death..
不喜欢被欺骗
doesn't like to be cheated.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
那是什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
你们现在最好小心点
You all just be careful now.
好吧 感谢你的提醒
Okay. Thanks for the advice!
怪胎
Creepy guy.
牛排 怎么样了 山姆? 就等你了
How's that foie gras, Sam? Waiting on you.
谢了
Thanks.
我的甜品好了吗?
Got my dessert?
这个有什么问题?
What's the matter with it?
他说太淡了 一点味道也没有
Said it was flat. No flavor.
- 他们想要换其它吗? - 没错
- Do they want something else? - Yeah.
检查下
The check.
我来尝一下
Let me taste it.
这个客人是个混蛋 味道挺好的
The customer is an asshole. The bourguignon is good.
等一下!
Hold on.
我能进来吗?
You mind if I come in?
当然 进来吧
Yeah. Sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
我以为你今晚工作
I thought you'd be working tonight.
是的 我第一班 但…
Yeah. You know, I worked the first shift, but..
我还有些需要做的事
there was something else I needed to do.
- 我能… - 哦
- Can I... - Oh.
当然 去吧
Yeah. Sure, go ahead.
谢谢
Thank you.
听着…
Listen ..
当桥塌陷的时候…
When everything started going down on that bridge..
…我唯一想的就是你
the only thing I thought about was you.
让你获得安全
Getting you to safety.
你是我唯一在乎的人 茉莉
You are the only thing I care about, Molly.
无论哪里出错了 我能改正
Whatever's wrong, I can fix it.
你没有做错什么
You haven't done anything wrong.
那 是什么?
Then, what? What is it?
巴黎
Paris.
我们说过这个
We talked about that.
我不会为了那份工作改变生活 离开你
I'm not going to uproot my life, leave you, for that job.
但那是你一直梦想的
But it's the only thing you've ever dreamed of.
人生苦短 山姆
Life is too short, Sam.
你应该做你想做的事
You have to go after what you love.
我在做
I am.
你应该接受份工作
You should take the job.
去巴黎
Go to Paris.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
不知道 我还没准备好 我感觉还没准备好
I don't know. I'm not ready. I don't feel ready.
真的很难集中精神
It's been really hard to concentrate after everything.
是吗? 你确定?
Yeah? Are you sure?
是
Yeah.
因为这是锦标赛前最后的训练
Because this is the last practice before the championship.
这是你选择学院的最后一次练习
And it's your last practice of your college career.
我知道 可是…
I know, but ..
我想你会做得好的
I think you got this.
- 真的吗? - 当然
- Really? - Yeah.
你喜欢它吧?
I mean, you love it out there.
好吧 你是对的
Okay. You're right.
除此之外 教练会杀了我 呵
And besides, coach would kill me. Heh.
呵呵
Heh.
给你
Here.
谢谢
Thanks.
过来
Come here.
拜
Bye.
你能做到的
You got this.
- 你应该更快一些 - 你需要再跟进
- You have to get a little more speed. - You gotta hit that follow-up.
- 我做后背伸展疼的厉害 - 是吗?
- I'm sore from the back extensions. - Really?
好吧 说真的 这太讨厌了
Okay, seriously, this is stupid.
他们应该把温度弄低点 要不我们都晕倒了
They've gotta make it cooler or we're gonna pass out.
他们在修理了
They're working on it.
他们应该现在把它修好
Well, they should have it fixed by now.
加油 坎蒂丝!
Come on, Candice. You're up.
加油 坎蒂丝!你能做到的!
Come on, Candice. You got this.
坎蒂丝 开始吧!
Candice, now.
这个真的很重要
Really strong value on this.
嗨 教练 这个怎么样?
Hey, coach! How was that?
我要你们照常从远道跑一次
I wanna see you guys run the routine all the way through once.
- 很好 - 呼
- That's good. - Whew.
珍妮 你是下一个!来吧
All right, Janine next. Let's go.
来吧 女士们 喝点水
Let's go, ladies, and drink water.
就这样!
That's it.
每次都这样 坎蒂丝
Every time, Candice.
- 给你 - 谢谢
- There you go. - Thanks.
太棒了 坎蒂丝
Nicely done, Candice.
好的 上高低杠吧
Okay, go to bars.
这次努力点 坎蒂丝
Go hard this time, Candice.
积极点
Let's be aggressive.
就这样 坎蒂丝 放松身体
Here we go, Candice. Stay loose.
好了 波特 到你了
Okay, Porter, it's your turn.
集中注意力
Stay focused.
好的
Good.
看着不错!坎蒂丝
Looking good, Candice.
坎蒂丝!坎蒂丝!
Candice? Candice?!
- 哦 怎么了? - 别碰她!
- Oh, what happened? - Don't touch her.
快打911
Someone call 911.
坎蒂丝?
Candice?
彼特
Peter.
我一听说就赶过来了
I came as soon as I heard.
她做的很好
She was doing great.
她就快要结束练习了 就…
She was almost finished with her routine and then ..
为什么发生这种事
Why did it happen?
根本没有任何征兆
This doesn't make any sense.
我不知道 兄弟
I don't know, man.
我很遗憾 很遗憾 彼特
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry, Peter.
我们走吧 山姆
Let's just go, Sam.
嘿
Hey.
你怎么样了?
How's it going?
很奇怪
It's weird.
这里… 很奇怪
Being here, I mean.
如此的安静
It's just so quiet.
丹尼斯已经转发了所有的来电
Yeah, well, Dennis had all the calls rerouted to corporate.
真令人沮丧
Yeah, well, it's depressing.
真垃圾 你们拿到抚恤金了吗?
Holy crap. Did you guys get your bereavement pay yet?
他在这里做什么?
Hey, what's he doing here?
我想他需要做些事分散注意力
I think he just needed the distraction.
是的
Yeah.
是的 关于坎蒂丝 真可惜
Yeah, that's a bummer about Candice.
我们都应该看到那件事发生
Guess we all should have seen that coming.
怎么了?
What?
你们看那些疯狂的体操员训练
You see the crazy shit those gymnasts do.
我奇怪这没有经常发生
I'm surprised it doesn't happen more often.
你已经处理了电子邮箱
Once you've handled the e-mail..
你还要停用已死员工的出入证
you'll need to deactivate all the key cards of the deceased employees.
相关说明在你的文件里
Instructions are in your binder.
这不是文件部经理的工作吗?
Well, shouldn't that be the job of the facility manager?
文件部的经理已经死了
The facility manager's dead.
丹尼斯 你想派人过来帮你吗?
Dennis, you want me to fly someone up there?
不 我可以自己处理
No, no, I got it.
噢 黛比!
Aw, Debbie.
你太下流了
You were so naughty.
去他的
Fuck it.
罗伯特 我的兄弟
Robert, my man.
啊
OW.
妈的
Shit.
你应该不需要了 兄弟
You shouldn't have, buddy.
兄弟 你在这里做什么?
Hey, man, what are you doing up here?
我要离开这个工厂 罗伊把我惹火了
Had to get off the factory floor, man. Roy's driving me crazy.
谁想来一个?
So, uh, who wants one?
哪来的?
Where'd you get these?
我从罗伊的车里偷出来的 呵呵 不错 是吧?
I stole it out of Roy's truck. Ha, ha. it's good, right? Ha, ha.
我有个更好的
I got something better.
这个不错
Ooh, nice one.
好 算我一个
Yeah, count me in.
你确定你要分享吗?
Are you sure you wanna share that?
如果不这样做 我只能独自饮酒 这更悲伤
If I don't, I'll end up drinking it alone, which is just sad.
这一天变得更有趣了
Well, this day just got way more fun.
不 我给你打电话了
No, I did call you.
当然 我立刻就给你打电话了 对吧
Of course. I just called you right now, didn't I?
因为我想再带你出来
Because I really do wanna take you out again.
是的 我们享用一个浪漫晚餐
Yeah, yeah, we'll do, like, a nice romantic dinner.
也许在郊外什么地方
You know, somewhere maybe outside the city.
等一下
Hold up.
你知道吗? 我得挂电话了
You know what? I gotta go.
不…不…不是和你分手
No, no, no. I'm not blowing you off.
听着 谁是我的女人 津博?
Hey, listen. Hey, who's my girl, Kimber?
安博 是的 我是这样说的
Amber, yes, that's what I said.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
(请关手机)
安博 抱歉 等一下
Amber? Amber, I'm sorry, wait a second.
声音听起来有点怪 是你那头 还是我的…
Is that weird sound on your end or mi...
对不起
Sorry about that.
有时候我的妹妹身边会有些流言蜚语
My, uh, sister tends to get a little chatty sometimes.
- 哦 - 嗯哼
- Uh-huh. - Uh-huh.
告诉我该怎样把缓解压力
So tell me about stress relief.
这个真的能给我带来什么帮助吗
And what does this really get me?
这个包括两种不同理疗
This covers a session for two different physical therapies.
例如按摩疗法?
Like massage therapy?
性爱按摩?
Erotic massage?
这是一个家族企业 所有的员工都是专业人士
This is a family operation. Everyone on staff is professional.
太棒了 我更喜欢专业的 事实上 我只是确认一下
That's great. I prefer a professional. In fact, I kind of demand it.
我只是想确认这个经验是否“专业” 最后会…
I'm just trying to clarify, though, that this professional experience ends, uh..
“快乐”
..happy.
我知道你真正需要的是什么
I know exactly what you need.
我确信你知道
Oh, I'm sure you do.
- 跟我走吧 请 - 我很乐意
- Follow me, please. - I'd love to.
哦 哦
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
别走得太快!
Slow down there a little bit.
是的 你的小裙子太可爱了
Yeah. Yeah, you have a lovely little Canter.
中国人都喜欢
Yum yum, dim sum.
等一下
Hold up there a second.
坚实的墙壁 我只是想确认一下
All right, these are solid. Just making sure.
总归会有点吵 如果你明白我的意思
Tend to be a bit noisy, if you know what I mean.
哈 佛陀 就像一个柔软的年糕
Ha, ha. Yo, Buddha. Slow down on the rice cakes.
- 闭上眼睛放松 - 嗯
- Just close your eyes. - Mm-hm.
- 放松 - 哦
- Relax. - Ooh.
很快会有人来为你服务的
And Someone will be in to service you soon.
好的
Oh, yeah.
好的 棒极了!
感觉顶呱呱
Feels dynamite.
不不 你弄错地方了 小姑娘
No, no. You're going the wrong way there, little lady.
我没走错房间
噢
Oh.
等下 不是那个年轻女孩子吗?
Wait a second, what happened to the younger version of you?
对不起 你有字幕吗?
Okay, I'm sorry. Do you come with subtitles?
也许我应该出去了
Maybe I should go.
我不知道你在这里说什么
Don't know what that means. No idea. Yep.
噢
OW!
你脖子被扭到了…
不要紧 不要紧 我没事
No, no, that's okay. That's okay, I'm all right.
该死的 你很强壮!
Holy shit, you're strong.
你在干嘛? 噢
What are you doing? Ow.
你相当的激动 不是吗?
You're a little aggressive. Isn't it?
“激动”那是什么意思?
What's "capay"? I don't know what that means.
我不知道那是什么意思 受够了
I don't want a "foo-hay." No "foo-hay." Aah!
干杯
Cheers.
该死 来接我了
Shit, that's my ride.
我必须得走了
Shit. I gotta go.
给我们留下更多了
Leaving more for us.
拜 再见
All right, bye.
- 再见 - 好
- See you later. - Okay.
回见
Later.
这个结束 接下来为什么干杯
This is the end, so, what are we toasting to?
为了大家找到新工作
To, uh, finding new jobs.
这里以后没多久就要关门大吉了
Because it's only a matter of time before they shut us down.
- 听听 - 哦 为了一个新的开始
- Hear, hear. - Oh. To starting over.
彼特
Peter?
这没有道理
It just doesn't make sense.
她在练习中死去 这样的事情
She dies doing something that she's done..
她生命的最后15年几乎每天都在做
almost every day for the last 15 years of her life.
她说她不想做
She said she didn't wanna do it.
她说她还没准备好
She said she wasn't ready.
我应该让她休息一下
And I should have stopped her.
我应该做些事情 我应该…
I should have done something. I should've..
彼特 你什么都没法做
Peter, there wasn't anything you could've done.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
对不起 很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
喂 布洛克警官 我是丹尼斯
Hello, Agent Block? This is Dennis.
彼特非常生气 我不知道原因
Yeah, Peter just freaked out about something, I don't know what.
这能说明什么吗?
Does that mean anything?
你让我说看到异常的事情就告诉你
You told me to call if I saw anything odd.
我不知道 谢谢你 丹尼斯 如果你看见奇怪的事就打给我
I don't know yet, but thank you, Dennis, and call me if you see anything strange.
更奇怪的事
Stranger.
我们也许应该有暗号 你认为呢?
Should we maybe have code names for one another, do you think?
完成
Over and out.
好了 告诉我它是怎样发生的?
All right, ahem, show me how this happened.
我没法说得清楚
I don't think I can.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
我是说 我尝试一百次 也无法重建事情的经过
I mean, I could try it a hundred times and never re-create exactly what happened here.
这是一个奇怪的失误
This is some freaky shit.
天呢
God!
事实上感觉挺好
Oh, that actually felt great.
还没做完呢 肥佬
哦 好极了
Oh, yeah. Awesome.
噢
Oh ..
等一下… 那些甚至已经消毒过了?
Wait. Are those things even sterilized?
如果你不做任何的消毒 可没法保证健康
No, no. I'm not catching any diseases unless I've earned them.
等等 你懂得我说的话
Wait a second. You understood that.
你会说英语
You speak English.
噢
Oh.
我当然能听懂 你以为我很蠢吗? 我只是假装不懂
你知道这个吗? 我们开始吧
All right, you know what? Let's do this.
二十亿人不可能都姓王
Two billion people can't be Wong.
我说王 你知道吗?
I said Wong. You follow me?
你知道的 你是中国人
You get it, you're Chinese.
哦 好了 进去了 绝对进去了 是 进去了
Ow, ow. Okay, it's in. it's definitely in. Ow, okay, yes, it is in.
你要在我身上放多少根针?
How many of these are you gonna put in me?
你能拿给我吗? 谢谢
Oh, uh, hey, can you grab that for me? Thanks.
治疗过程中不许打电话
嘿
Hey.
你一点都不友好 你知道嘛
That's not very nice, you know.
这根针将可以帮助你生发的
好好休息30分钟 你会觉得很舒服的
你把手指插入到我眼睛里了
Okay, your thumbs are kind of in my eyes.
女士你真的很烦哎
I'm not gonna lie, it's a little annoying.
我再说一次女士 我真的不知道你在说什么
Once again, Chinese lady, I don't have a clue what you're saying.
我很迷惑
I'am loose so.
只是让你睡30分钟
Thirty minutes. You sleep.
睡觉
Sleep.
哦
Oh.
嘿 着火了!
Hey! Fire!
有人吗?
Hello?!
嘿
Hey!
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey!
嘿 这里着火了!
Hey, there's a fire in here!
嘿 这着火了!
Hey, there's a fire!
进来
Get in here!
妈的!
Oh, shit.
- 你们应该和我一起过来 - 去巴黎?
- You should come with me. - To Paris?
是的 你自己说的 比如 你要重新开始
Yeah, you know, you said it yourself. Like, you're gonna have to start over.
和我重新开始
Start over with me.
你到底要喝几杯?
How many drinks have you had?
不 茉莉 我是说真的
Enough. Molly, I'm serious.
你是对的 如果我不去工作 我会后悔
Look, you were right. If I don't take the job, I'll regret it.
但我不想失去你
But I'm not willing to lose you.
为何我要选择其中之一
Why does it have to be one or the other?
我更希望你和我在一起
I'm better when you're with me.
伙计们 你们没法相信这个
Uh, guys, you're not gonna believe this.
他们说那是一场意外
They're saying it was a freak accident.
如果你觉得是这样那你举起手
Yeah, raise your hand if you believe that.
谁死在按摩院? 说真的
Who dies during a massage? Seriously.
首先是坎蒂丝 现在是艾萨克
First Candice, now Isaac.
这不可能是一个巧合
It can't be a coincidence.
这不是巧合
It's not.
你要去哪?
Where are you going?
真是奇怪的家伙
It's that creepy dude.
为何要跟着我们?
Why are you following us?
你是谁?
Who are you?
你去过墓地 然后体操训练室 现在又到这里
You were at the cemetery, then the gym, now here.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我的工作
My job.
(验尸官)
我们发生了什么事?
What's happening to us?
是什么让你认为我知道一些事?
What makes you think I know anything?
你警告过我们
You warned us.
在墓地 你说死神不喜欢被欺骗
At the memorial service. You said Death didn't like to be cheated.
- 因为我之前见到过 - 你看见了什么?
- It's just that I've seen this before. - See what?
一次灾难中的幸存者
A lucky few survive a disaster.
然后接连不断的被死神夺去生命
And then one by one, Death comes for them all.
你改变了吊桥的事
You changed things on that bridge.
现实难题是 你再次死于不同的方式
There's a wrinkle in reality. And that wrinkle is you.
什么? 我们注定要死?
So, what, we're doomed to die?
我是说 是这样吗?
I mean, is that it?
我们只是救了自己 你说的是什么废话?
We just got our lives back, so, what kind of fucked up karma is that?
你是说我们没法阻止?
Are you say we can't stop this?
你们本该在吊桥中全部死去
You were supposed to die on that bridge.
你们都不应该出现在这里
You're not supposed to be here.
你欺骗了死神
You shorted Death.
他就会让其他人替你死去
So you let Death have somebody else in your place..
然后你取代他生存的领域
and then you take their spot in the realm of the living.
所有他们可以生存的时间
All the days and years that they have yet to live.
而他们代替你们死去
And they take your place in death.
为了保持生死的平衡
Then the books are balanced.
等等 我们杀了别人 可以得到他们的生存?
Wait a minute. We kill someone, we get their life?
这就是你要告诉我们的?
Is that what you're telling me?
不是我制定的规则
I don't make the rules.
我只负责清除"游戏"之后的
I just clean up after the game is over.
也许这就是为什么坎蒂丝和艾萨克会死了
Maybe that's why Candice and Isaac are dead.
他们本不应该活着 现在跟随我们剩下的人了
They weren't supposed to survive, and now it's coming after the rest of us.
不
No.
不 不是我们所有的人
No, not all of us.
茉莉逃掉了 她没有死
Molly made it, she didn't die.
什么?
What?
当我看见幻象时 出现预感时 不管是什么
Well, when I had that vision, or premonition, or whatever it was..
在吊桥坍塌之前我帮你穿过去了
I got you across before the bridge collapsed.
你活了下来
You survived.
你救了她?
You saved her?
为什么? 因为你觉得她比其他人更值得你去救?
Why, because you decided that she deserved to live more than the rest of us?
那不是他所说的意思 我不应该比其他人更好的活着
That's not what he's saying. I don't deserve to live more than anyone.
她似乎比坎蒂丝更值得你去救
You deserve to live more than Candice.
噢 彼特 等等!
Whoa, Peter, hang on.
伙计们 拜托
No, look, guys, come on.
你没喝苦艾酒 是吗?
You're not drinking the Kool-Aid, are you?
杀别人让自己活着 死亡名单 真的吗?
Killing people to survive. Death's list. Really?
我也许不知道发生了什么 但不是那家伙说的
I may not know what's going on, but it's not what that guy's selling.
是吗? 那我们之后怎么办?
Yeah? What else is it, then?
妈的
Shit.
我必须找到奥莉维亚
We need to tell Olivia.
快点
Come on.
我的表单已经填过了
My forms are all signed.
你第一次诊断到现在 已经有段时间了
I see that it's been quite a while since your first consultation.
今天为何突然决定要做手术?
What made you decide to take the leap today?
呃 经历了太多事情
Uh, well, a lot is going on in my life..
我不想错过任何事
and I just don't wanna miss anything..
你知道的 很重要的
you know, important.
同样原因 我亲自来做
Same reason I had it done myself.
- 快回来 我们就开始 - 好的
- Come on in back. Let's get you started. - Okay.
哦
Oh.
是的 这是第一步 你将不再需要这些了
Yep, that's the first step. You'll never need those again.
我们到了 进来
Here we are. Come on in.
这些是干嘛的?
What's with these?
这是为了照顾年轻的患者
Oh, just for some of our younger patients.
有时也给年龄大的患者 来吧
And, um, sometimes our older ones too. Come on.
那是什么?
What was that?
放松点
Relax.
你知道 它看起来比实际上要糟
You know, it looks a lot worse than it really is.
我会将头慢慢的移动
Okay, I'm gently going to position your head..
你要告诉我
and I want you to tell me..
当它感觉足够紧时
when this feels snug.
我无法移动我的头了
I can't move my head.
完美 这就是我们想要的
Perfect. Just what we want.
准备开始
There we go.
进行有趣的部分 先滴一滴麻醉剂
Okay, now comes the fun part. Here comes a drop.
你的眼睛会有轻微的麻木感
And you will feel a little numbness in your eye..
这是个好东西
which is a good thing.
深呼吸
Deep breath.
放松
Relax.
非常好
Very good.
棒极了 女孩
Thatta girl.
好了
There.
还不算太糟 是吧?
That's not so bad, is it?
看起来不错
Looks good.
- 那是什么? - 放松 奥莉维亚
- What was that? - Just relax, Olivia.
我要输入有关一些数据
I'm just gonna enter some data into ..
托蒂
Dottie!
托…
Dot..
知道吗 我的助手给了我一份不完整的档案
Do you know what? My assistant's given me an incomplete file.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
等等 你离开了?
Hold on, you're leaving?!
这是正常情况吗?
Is that supposed to be happening?!
(紧急停止)
救命!
Help me!
奥莉维亚 卡斯特 她在哪里?
Olivia Castle. Where is she?
她可能处境危险
She might be in danger.
她很好 我们一直做这种眼部手术
She's fine. We do this kind of procedure all the time.
救救我
Help me!
救救我!
之前从没发生过这种事
This has never happened before.
山姆
Sam.
今晚请和我待在一起
Stay with me tonight, please.
当然可以
Of course.
5个不同的保护系统全部失效
Five different systems had to go wrong..
自然雷射放射太强烈了 5个
for that laser to fail us so spectacularly. Five.
你想从我们这得到什么
What do you want from us?
我让你告诉我 你认为发生什么了
I want you to tell me what you think is going on.
死了2个? 好吧 这是巧合
Two deaths? Okay, all right. That's a coincidence.
3个? 这是个模式
Three? That's a pattern.
现在
Now..
我知道你俩个不会做这个
I know you two didn't do this.
是吗?
All right?
但我认为你知道一些事情
But I think you know something.
那是什么?
What is it?
我们什么都不知道
We don't know anything.
猜测一下
Take a guess.
我们认为不应该在桥上活下来
We think we weren't supposed to survive on that bridge.
什么?
What?
现在一些事情在试着纠正它
And now something is trying to set it right.
一些事情?
"Something"?
这就是你所知道的?
That's all you got?
到现在为止 是这样
Right now, yeah.
如果你找到了其他的解释 让我们知道
But if you come up with any other explanations, let us know.
谢谢
Thank you.
一些事情
"Something."
嗨
Hey.
起来很久了?
Been up long?
不知道 我睡不着 我一直在想吊桥的事
Uh, I don't know. I couldn't sleep. I just kept thinking about the bridge.
山姆 你自己没办法解决的
Sam, you can't do this to yourself.
不 不 我在想 在感应中…
No. No, no, no. I was thinking about, in the premonition..
我们都下了公交车 整条路和桥都塌陷了
we all got off the bus, but the ground gave way and Candice fell.
接着汽车翻覆
Then the bus tipped over.
艾萨克 他没有下车… 他和车掉了下去
And Isaac, he never got off the bus. He went with it.
你弄清什么了?
What are you getting at?
我知道发生了太多的事情
I know that there was just so much going on ..
我知道我帮你过去的
Look, I know that I helped you across.
之后我返回去找奥维利亚
Then I reached back for Olivia.
但是她没活下来 她掉了下去
But she didn't make it. She fell.
所以第一个是坎蒂丝
So first was Candice.
然后是艾萨克
Then Isaac.
再之后是奥莉维亚
Then Olivia.
他们按顺序死了
They're dying in order.
奥莉维亚之后是谁?
Who dies after Olivia?
罗伊 请来中控室
Roy, would you come to the control room, please?
- 罗伊 老板找你了 - 你麻烦大了 罗伊
- Uh-oh, Roy, that's the boss. - You in trouble, Roy.
好吧 学生仔 你到底想和我说什么?
Okay, schoolboy, what do you wanna talk to me about?
- 在说你的考勤表 - 是的 在说考勤表
- What is with your timecard? - Let's talk about my timecard.
你少算了我的时间 意味着你少算了我的工资
You out my hours, which means you cut my pay!
我去掉了所有人的时间 好吧
I cut everyone's hours, okay?
这事之后管理层减少我们至少百分之五十工作
Corporate has us operating at less than 50 percent until this thing blows over.
我的赌本 不止百分之五十工作
My bookie ain't operating at 50 percent.
- 我孩子不会只工作百分之五十的 - 罗伊
- My dumb kid ain't operating at 50 percent. - Roy.
我前妻 她拿百分之五十 我告诉你我要做什么
My ex-wife, she's taking 50 percent, so I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
不 我们要离开这 伙计
No, we gotta move, man.
- 嘿 我哪也不去 - 我们得离开这! 得离开这
- Hey, I'm not going anywhere. Hey! - Look, we gotta move! Gotta move!
你必须离开!
We gotta move now!
罗伊 你还好吧?
Roy! You okay down there?
- 丹尼斯 - 嗨
- Hey, Dennis? - Hey.
他们关闭这里了
They're closing us down.
他们关闭工厂了?
They're shutting down the plant?
不是工厂 只有我们 只有销售和管理部门
Not the plant, just us. Just sales and administration.
你能相信我们吗? 解雇我们?
Can you believe it? Us?
一般都是在工厂伙计被解雇的
I mean, It's the factory guys that usually get laid off.
不是我们 我觉得我们是安全的
Not us, we're supposed to be safe.
丹尼斯 我们有更大麻烦了
Yeah, Dennis, we got bigger problems.
奥莉维亚和艾萨克死了
Olivia and Isaac are dead.
谁是艾萨克?
Who's Isaac?
艾萨克帕默 技术员
Isaac Palmer, tech support.
不是已经死了吗?
Wasn't he dead already?
没有 丹尼斯
No, Dennis.
听我说… 我们也会和他们一样的 除非我们做什么
Listen, it's going to happen to us too if we don't do something about it.
我懂你的意思 听着 这被称为"幸存者内疚"
Yeah, I understand. Listen, it's called survivor's guilt.
不是这样的 内疚并不会死亡
No. No, guilt doesn't kill you.
很明显 你没有遇到我的岳父母
Obviously, you've never met my in-laws.
我不是开玩笑 丹尼斯!
I'm not fucking around here, Dennis.
任何人可能是下一个
Anyone could be next.
有可能是你! 听懂了吗?
It could be you. Understand?
没有人是安全的
Nobody's safe.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
吊桥倒塌 我们本不应该活着
We weren't supposed to survive that bridge collapse.
现在只有杀人或者被杀
And so now it's kill or be killed.
懂了吗 丹尼斯?
You get that, Dennis?
随便了
Whatever.
我警告你了 随便你想做什么
I warned you. Do whatever you wanna do.
我会的
I Will.
嗨 布洛克警官 是我 丹尼斯 呃
Hey, Agent Block, it's Dennis. Um..
彼特 到我这里来过 完全失控了
Listen, Pete just came in here and he's just completely lost it.
嚷着一会说谋杀 一会说被杀
He's yelling about "kill or be killed."
是啊 听起来像是个威胁
Oh, yeah, it definitely sounded like a threat.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
我不知道 不知道 发生得太快了
I don't know. I don't know. It just happened so fast.
- 内森 你还好吗? - 我还好
- Nathan. Are you okay? - Yeah.
- 当我听到时我在想… - 不 我很好
- We heard, and we thought.. - No. No, uh, I'm good.
你杀了他?
Did you kill him?
什么
What?
不 我只是…
No. No, I just..
那只是个巧合 他正好在那…
It was just timing, you know? He got in the way and..
不 你杀了他 不是吗?
No, you did, didn't you?
你预见了 你杀了他 你让他代替你
You saw it coming, and then you took his life. You put him in the way.
我真的什么也没做
No, I didn't really do anything.
- 说实话 你做了还是没做? - 彼特 冷静点
- Tell ture, Did you or didn't you? - Hey, Peter, calm down.
你做了还是没做?
Did you or didn't you?
是的 我想我做了
Yes. I think I did.
我杀了他
I killed him.
假如理论成立 你找个替死鬼
So if the theory works, then you traded spots.
他替你死了 你得到了生命
He should have your death, and you should have his years.
我们怎么能够肯定?
How do we know for sure?
我觉得有个死亡顺序
I think there's an order to these deaths.
这个映射吊桥的死亡顺序
They mirror the order everyone died in on the bridge.
那谁是下一个?
Then who would be next?
谁能第一个告诉我这件事是怎么发生的?
Who wants to be first to tell me what the hell happened?
是谁? 山姆
Who is it, Sam?
谁是什么?
Who's what?
丹尼斯! 是丹尼斯!
Dennis! It was Dennis.
真该死!
No shit.
天
Jesus.
为何要和我争论?
Why are you fighting me on this?
你真的不想去工作 是吗?
You're not seriously going to work, are you?
茉莉 艾萨克死于按摩床
Molly, Isaac died on a massage table.
如果死神来找我 无论我在哪里都一样
If Death is gonna come for me, I don't think it matters where I am.
你必须做些什么事情
You have to do something.
- 杀了他人来救自己? - 不 当然不是
- What, kill someone so I can live? - No, of course not.
我们在想其他的办法
We'll just have to figure something else out.
我已经想出来了
I have figured it out.
有些事情把我从桥上救出来
Something saved me on that bridge.
或许他根本没想让我死
Maybe it doesn't want me to die.
或许
Maybe.
茉莉 我们不能活在恐惧中
We can't live our lives in fear, Moll.
所以 如果明天或在50年之后会死 没关系
So if it happens tomorrow, or 50 years from now, whatever.
如果我们在一起
As long as we're together..
我会很开心的
I'll be okay.
好不? 为什么不在下班后过来
Right? Why don't you come by after my shift..
为你准备一顿丰盛的晚餐 好吗?
and I'll make you a nice late dinner, okay?
把那个给我
All right, give me this.
- 抱歉 - 我们一定要等他们吗 是吗?
- Excuse me. - We don't have to wait for them, do we?
- 我会告诉你的 - 谢谢
- I'll let you know. - Okay, thank you.
小牛肉好了 拿出去
Veal's ready, take it out.
山姆 该开工了
Samuel. Get to work on the bourguignon.
喔
Whoa.
锅 借过
Pan coming through.
哦 小心
Whoa, watch yourself.
- 好的 肉来了 放起来 恩? - 是 先生
- Okay. Meat's in. Pick it up, eh? - Yes, sir.
噢
Whoa.
这可能会变得很糟 哈哈
That could've been ugly, huh? Ha, ha.
是的 可能
Yeah. Could've been.
文森 快点 好不?
Vincent, speed it up, okay?
哦 嘿
Whoa, hey!
嘿 清理下炉子
Hey, clean that grate.
- 碰见你女朋友了 - 哦
- Just met your girlfriend. - Oh.
我想给她煮些东西 可以吗?
Are you sure it's okay if I make her a little something?
弄好之后清理干净吧
Make sure to clean up afterward.
我会的 当然 谢谢
I will, of course. Thank you.
- 大厨 还有… - 什么事?
- And, chef .. - What ?
员工实习…
The apprenticeship.
如果录用仍有效
If the offer still stands..
我愿意接受
I'd like to take it.
是你的了
It's yours.
嗯 没太多的悬念
Okay, no more suspense.
这是你所期望的
What you've been waiting for.
哦 你能帮我消灭点吗
Wow. You're gonna help me with this, right?
当然 如果你想…
Yeah, sure, if you want me to..
你不想
No? You don't want me to...
你的法语怎么样
So how's your French?
呵 很差
Heh. Terrible.
很好 我们可以一起差了
Oh, good. Well, then, we can be terrible together.
- 为什么? - 我接受了员工实习
- Why? - I took the internship.
什么? 山姆 太不可思议
What? Sam, that's amazing.
我太为你感到骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
- 彼特 - 嗨
- Peter. - Hey.
你还好吗? 你看起来很不高兴
You okay, man? You look a little, uh, upset.
是 是 这几天我过的有些艰难
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Just a rough couple days.
是的 所有人都是
Yeah. Yeah, for everyone.
有人过的比其他人好
For some more than others.
我可以进来吗?
Do you mind if I come in?
哦 当然 进来吧
Oh, yeah, of course. Yeah, come in.
来 坐吧
Here, have a seat.
谢谢
Thanks.
你好 彼特
Hey, Peter.
嗨 茉莉
Hi, Molly.
彼特 想来一些吃的吗? 我可以给你做些通心粉
Peter, can I get you anything to eat? I can make you up some pasta.
不 不用 我很好 谢谢!
Uh, no. No, no, no. I'm good. Uh, thank you.
抱歉 我在想事情…
Uh, I'm sorry. I just thought..
彼特 很高兴你在这 你不该独自一个在这的
Peter, It's good that you're here. You shouldn't be alone right now.
你知道 我很奇怪还能在这
Yeah, you know, I'm surprised I'm here at all.
呃
Uh ..
仍然活着 我意思是…
Still alive, I mean.
我是下一个 对吧
I'm next to go, right?
我 然后是你 是吗?
It's me and then you, isn't it?
不管怎样 我考虑了整个晚上
Anyways, uh, I was up all last night, you know..
考虑假如我真的这么做
thinking about if I could really do it.
- 做什么? - 结束某个人的生命
- Do what? - Take someone else's life.
如果我真的杀了某个陌生人 让我代替他们活着
If I could actually kill some stranger, replace their life with my own.
我思考这个
And I thought about it.
我确信自己…
And I convinced myself that..
对 我可以做到
yeah, I could.
所以我走在街上
So I went on a walk.
你知道 不是特别的地方
You know, nowhere in particular...
每隔几分钟 都有机会自己出现
but every couple of minutes, an opportunity would just present itself
不断的
Heh. Like clockwork.
我可以追某人 把他追进一个死胡同
I could just grab somebody and pull them into an alley.
或者推路边某人到车流中
Or just shove somebody off a curb into traffic.
你知道吗?
You know?
真的很容易
It'd be real easy.
彼特 你做了什么?
Peter, what did you do?
- 你… - 不 我没做
- Did you... - No, I didn't.
我做不出来
I couldn't.
我意识到…
I realized that..
我不能杀死另一个人 那个人不应该死
I couldn't kill somebody that didn't deserve to die.
我想到了坎蒂丝 我想 等一下
And I thought about Candice, and I thought, "Wait a minute.
坎蒂丝她也不该死
Candice didn't deserve to die.
奥莉维亚或丹尼斯不都应该死
Olivia didn't. Dennis didn't.
我也不应该死
I don't."
我应该死吗?
Do I?
不 当然不应该
No, of course you don't.
好吧
Well..
我们之中没有人应该死 那么为什么…
none of us deserve to die, then why is it..
你应该活下去 茉莉?
that you deserve to live, Molly?
像你自己说的那样
You said it yourself..
你不应该活着
you don't.
快走
Go!
重复 枪战 请求增援 华盛顿1026号
Repeat, shots fired. Requesting backup. 1026 Washington.
藏起来!我引开他 能走的时候 走!
Hide and I'll distract him. When you can, go.
还没完呢 山姆
Not done yet, Sam.
她在哪里?
Where is she?
- 她在哪里? - 彼特 我不会让你伤害她
- Where is she?! - I'm not gonna let you hurt her, Peter.
首先你必须杀了我
You're gonna have to kill me first.
那对我没什么好处
Well, that doesn't do me any good. Heh, heh.
死神也跟在你们身后
Death's after you too.
这太疯狂了 彼特 别这么做!
This is crazy, Peter. Don't do this.
好好考虑一下 好吗?
Just think for a minute, all right?
你不是凶手
You are not a killer.
我不想杀死任何人 山姆
I don't wanna kill anybody, Sam.
可是我也不想死
I don't wanna die yet either.
呵 还没轮到你
Heh. It's not your time yet.
别担心 茉莉
Don't worry, Molly..
我没杀他
I didn't kill him.
但不需要这样做 茉莉 因为…
But I didn't need to, Molly..Because..
因为 死神找的是我
Because Death is gonna do that for me.
这并不意味着我不能帮忙
Doesn't mean I can't help it.
就这样
That's it.
- 你还好吗? 怎么了? - 彼特 他有一把枪
- Are you okay? What's going on? - It's Peter. He has a gun.
天啊!
Oh, my God.
你杀了他
You killed him.
该轮到山姆了
It's Sam's turn.
彼特 你走吧
Peter, just go.
你杀了布洛克 你现在安全了
You have Block's life, you're safe now.
求你了
Please.
对不起 茉莉
I'm sorry, Molly.
可是你刚才看到一个联邦探员被杀了
But you just witnessed the murder of a federal agent.
我不想在监狱度过我刚换来的命
And I'm not gonna spend the life I just earned in prison.
茉莉 快点跑 去求救!
Molly, go! Go get help!
王八蛋
You son of a bitch!
告诉坎蒂丝 我爱她
Tell Candice I love her.
彼特!
Peter.
他不见了 你杀了他
It's gone. You killed him.
这意味着 我得到布洛克的命
So does that mean I get Block's life?
是的
Yeah.
我猜是的
I guess I do.
(两周之后)
我可以坐在窗户旁边吗?
Do you mind if I take the window seat?
- 你想让我坐在中间? - 恩
- Are you kidding me? You're gonna make me sit in the middle? - Uh-huh.
- 你开玩笑吗? 我的比你大两倍 - 不是吧
- I'm like twice your size. - Not really.
好了
All right.
- 我要杀了他 - 妈的 我要…
- I'll remove him. - Fuck you. I'll remove..
放开他
Get off him!
镇定下来
Settle down!
- 快点 要爆炸了 快 你个笨蛋 - 快下飞机!
- Come on, Browning! Come on, you punk! - Get off the plane!
快下飞机 你们不明白
Get off the plane. You don't understand!
大家请坐好
Everybody just stay where you are.
- 那里怎么了? - 我也不清楚
- What's all that about? - I have no idea.
女士们 先生们 我们即将开始…
Ladies and gentlemen, we'll be pulling away from the gate as..
我们要起飞了
Here we go.
起飞时客舱光线会调暗
The cabin lights have been dimmed for takeoff
∮ 风中灰尘 ∮
∮ Dust in the wind ∮
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
非常抱歉
Oh, excuse me.
之前下飞机的乘客 是怎么回事?
Those passengers who got off the plane earlier, what was that all about?
一个孩子恐慌症发作了 想离开飞机
A kid had a panic attack and wanted off the plane.
他说他看到了幻象
Said he had some kind of vision.
不!
No.
我的天啊!
Oh, my God!
山姆!
Sam.
我抓到你了!
I got you!
- 山姆! - 茉莉 抓紧!
- Sam! - Molly, hold on!
不!
No!
很高兴见到你来 内森
Nice of you to come, Nathan.
我知道罗伊不是很容易共事
I know Roy wasn't the easiest guy to work with.
你知道
You know.
然而 我不能相信他就这样死了
I still can't believe he's gone, though.
是的 是 不开玩笑
Yeah. Yeah, no kidding.
我觉得这结果更好
I guess it was for the best.
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
为了保险的原因 他们做了尸检
Company did an autopsy for insurance purposes.
查出来罗伊的脑血管扩大
Turns out Roy had an enlarged blood vessel in his brain so big..
产生的血管破裂 他们说他们随时会死的
it was about to burst. They said he'd be dead any day now.
随时?
Any day?
这他妈就是生活
Life's a bitch.
你们都要小心点
You all just be careful now.